Guide to the Stanford University, Provost's Office, Records
Stanford University. Libraries.
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Stanford University, Provost's Office, records
1963-2010
SC0150
Stanford University. Office of the Provost. Office of Budget and Management..
Stanford University. Vice Provost for Budget Planning.
Stanford University. Vice Provost for Management and Budget.
71 Linear feet
Records of Vice Provost Raymond F. Bacchetti consist of correspondence, memoranda, minutes of meetings relating to the Budget Adjustment Program (BAP), 1970-1975; records for the academic year 1972-1973, including correspondence, memoranda, salary charts and graphs of income and expenditures; correspondence and memoranda relating to Black and Chicano students at Stanford, 1970-1971.
Department of Special Collections and University Archives Green Library 557 Escondido Mall Stanford, CA 94305-6064 Email: specialcollections@stanford.edu Phone: (650) 725-1022 URL: http://library.stanford.edu/spc
Administrative Information
Provenance
Administrative transfer, Office of the Provost, 1976, 2011.
Information about Access
Restricted 20 years from tenure of provost.
Description of the Collection
Records of Vice Provost Raymond F. Bacchetti consist of correspondence, memoranda, minutes of meetings relating to the Budget Adjustment Program (BAP), 1970-1975; records for the academic year 1972-1973, including correspondence, memoranda, salary charts and graphs of income and expenditures; correspondence and memoranda relating to Black and Chicano students at Stanford, 1970-1971.
This collection is divided into three series: the records of the Budget Adjustment Program (BAP), 1970-1975, which make up the largest part of this collection; the budget for the academic year 1972-1973; and Minority Affairs.
SERIES ONE: The Budget Adjustment Program was designed in 1969 in response to the patterns of university expenditures and income, which were rapidly draining the university's financial reserves. The original BAP goal was to reduce the university's operating budget vase by $2,500,000 over a four-year period from 1970 to 1974. But at the end of 1970, it was realized that this goal was based upon an overly optimistic economic viewpoint, and BAP was revised to save $6,000,000 over a five year period from 1970 to 1975.
BAP was divided into five phases, each one academic year long, and identified by a Roman numeral. Thus BAP I covered the year 1970-1971, BAP II, 1971-1972, etc. Within each of these phases, a specific university wide reducation goal was to be met. This sum was then broken down, and each school and department was assigned its own budget reduction goal, to be achieved by internal reorganization of priorities for greater operational economy. This collection, composed of memoranda, correspondence, and agenda and minutes of meetings, reflects the financial conditions in which many colleges and universities found themselves in the late 1960's, and the solutions proposed by one such institution.
SERIES TWO: The second series consists of the background materials used in the preparations of the university budget for the year 1972-1973. It contains interdepartmental memoranda, correspondence, salary charts, and graphs of income and expenditures relevant to budget planning in every phase of Stanford University's operations.
SERIES THREE: The third series, Minority Affairs, deals with the concerns of Black and Chicano students at Stanford in 1970-1971. Included are memoranda on budgeting for funding of Black and Chicano Studies programs, hiring of minority faculty members, minority admissions, correspondence from the Black Student Union (BSU), and Mecha, the Chicano students' organization, and newspaper clippings collected by Mr. Bacchetti on topics concerning minority students.
Arrangement note
The collection is arranged in four series and two additions: 1. Budget Adjustment Program (BAP) 1970-1975, 2. Budget 1972-1973, 3. Minority affairs 1970-1971, 4. Office of Management and Budget.
Access Terms
Bacchetti, Raymond F., 1934-; Stanford University. Budget Adjustment Program.; Stanford University. Office of the Provost. Office of Budget and Management..; Stanford University. Vice Provost for Budget Planning.; Stanford University. Vice Provost for Management and Budget.; College administrators.; Stanford University--Administration.; Universities and colleges--Administration.
Collection Contents
- Budget Adjustment Program (BAP), 1970-1975; Series 1
  The Budget Adjustment Program was designed in 1969 in response to the patterns of university expenditures and income, which were rapidly draining the university's financial reserves. The original BAP goal was to reduce the university's operating budget vase by $2,500,000 over a four-year period from 1970 to 1974. But at the end of 1970, it was realized that this goal was based upon an overly optimistic economic viewpoint, and BAP was revised to save $6,000,000 over a five year period from 1970 to 1975.
  BAP was divided into five phases, each one academic year long, and identified by a Roman numeral. BAP I covered the year 1970-1971, BAP II, 1971-1972, etc. Within each of these phases, a specific university-wide reducation goal was to be met. This sum was then broken down, and each school and department was assigned its own budget reduction goal, to be achieved by internal reorganization priorities for greater operational economy. This collection, composed of memoranda, correspondence, and agenda and minutes of meetings, reflects the financial conditions in which many colleges and and universities found themselves in the late 1960's, and the solutions proposed by one such institution.
  Records are arranged alphabetically by school or department, and within each school, chronologically.
  - BAP I, 1970-1971
    - General overview (Box 1, Folder 1)
      Materials dealing with BAP's universitywide functions and goals. Also in this folder: Financial breakdown by schools - Business, Earth Sciences, Engineering Humanities and Sciences.
    - Schools: (con't) Law, Medicine. Miscellaneous programs - Hoover Institution, student services. (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - BAP II, 1971-1972
    - General overview (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - General overview (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Financial breakdown by schools: Earth Sciences (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Financial breakdown by schools: Engineering, Education, Graduate School of Business, Medicine, Law (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Financial breakdown by schools: Humanities and Sciences (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Humanities and Sciences, (con't) (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - BAP III, 1972-1973
    - General overview (Box 2, Folder 2)
      Agenda and minutes of meetings.
    - Final report, with correspondence generated by its publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Administration: Business and Finance (vice president for), General Secretary's Office, President's/Provosts' Office, Graduate Studies, Undergraduate Studies (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Cost analyses of xerox photocopying and its alternatives, and of long-distance telephone charges (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Admissions, Athletics, Business Affairs, buildings and grounds (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Health Physics, Housing, Planning, Purchasing (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Health Physics continued (specifically radiological protection) insurance, safety and health (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Committe on International Studies, Chapel, Dean of Students (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Health Service, Financial Aids (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Food Research Institute, General Secretary's Office, Graduate Studies, Hoover Institution (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - University libraries, overseas campuses, personnel (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - President's Office, Registrar, Vice President for Research, summer session (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Undergraduate Studies, university relations (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Memos and charts on: Cost sharing, fund designation, investments, internal debt (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Tuition (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Travel, phones, xerox. Staff benefits (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Financial breakdown by schools: Business, Earth Sciences, Education, Engineering, Humanities and Sciences, Law, Medicine (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Schedule and planning (Box 5, Folder 1)
      Committee meeting agenda and minutes.
    - Agenda and minutes (con't) (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Agenda and minutes (con't) (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - BAP IV, 1973-1974
    - Index. General Overview. Agenda. Final report and details (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - By Schools: Earth Sciences, Education, Engineering, Graduate School of Business, Humanities and Sciences, Law, Medicine. Alternatives. Admissions, Center for Research on International Studies, Chapel (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Food Research Institute, Hoover Institution, Overseas Campuses Physical Education, Registrar, Student Health service, summer session, Tresidder Union, University libraries. Business and Finance, cost sharing, General Secretary's Office, Graduate studies, President's Office, Undergraduate studies, University relations, Xerox (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - BAP V, 1974-1975
    - Final recommendation. Agenda. Financial breakdown by schools; Business, Earth Sciences, Education, Engineering (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Schools continued: Humanities and Sciences, Law, Medicine. Cost sharing, Food Research Institute, Dean of Student Affairs, Graduate admissions, Registrar, Prisident's Office, Business and Finance, University relations, Reallocation reserves (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Budget, 1972-1973; Series 2
  The second series consists of the background materials used in the preparations of the university budget for the year 1972-1973. It contains interdepartmental memoranda, correspondence, salary charts, and graphs of income and expenditures relevant to budget planning in every phase of Stanford University's operations.
  - Budget 1971-1972 revisions (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Schedule - Budget Advisory Group agenda and minutes (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Procedure. 1972-1973 committments. 1972-1973 expenditures. 1972-1973 income. (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Admissions, Business and Finance, Chapel, Dean of Students, Financial Aid (graduate) (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Financial Aid (undergraduate), Food Research Institute, Graduate Studies (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Hoover Institutions, Library, overseas campuses (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Physical Education, President's Office, Registrar, research (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - SLAC, summer session, undergraduate studies (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Schools: Earth Sciences, Education, Engineering (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Graduate School of Business (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Humanities and Sciences (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Law, Medicine (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Minority affairs, 1970-1971; Series 3
  The third series, Minority Affairs, deals with the concerns of Black and Chicano students at Stanford in 1970-1971. Included are memoranda on budgeting for funding of black and Chicano Studies programs, hiring of minority faculty members, minority admissions, correspondence from the Black Student Union (BSU), and Mecha, the Chicano students' organization, and newspaper clippings collected by Mr. Bacchetti on topics concerning minority students.
  - Minority Affairs: Black (Box 8, Folder 1)
    Interdepartmental memoranda and correspondence on budgeting for Black Studies Program. Correspondence from the Black Students' Union, including list of demands, and the administration's response.
  - Minority Affairs: Black. (con't) (Box 8, Folder 2)
    Discussions of funding for the hiring of Black faculty members.
  - Minority Affairs: Black. (con't) (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Mirrority Affairs: Chicano (Box 8, Folder 4)
    Memoranda and correspondence on Chicano Studies Programs. Correspondence from Mecha.
  - Minority Affairs: Chicano (Box 8, Folder 5)
    Dealing with admissions and hiring.
  - Minority Affairs: Chicano. (con't) (Box 8, Folder 6)
- Office of Management and Budget, Series 4
  - Management development program, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Budget process, 1976-1977 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Budget process, 1978-1979 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Budget process, 1980-1981 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Department of French and Italian, report, 1972 Jun 15 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Daily file, APO staff, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Daily file, W. Price, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Daily file misc., 1978 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Daily file R.F. Bacchetti, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - BIT AD HOC Committee Meeting, 1978 Feb (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Long range forecast, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Statistical study of the curriculum, 1975-1976 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Statistical study of the curriculum, 1976-1977 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Reports on undergraduate education, 1976-1977 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Financial reports: Brown University, USC, MIT, University of Chicago, 1979 Jun (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Academic Council, 1974-1975
    - Committee on Committees, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Committee on Professoriate, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Academic programs, 1972-1975
    - Childhood and society, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Courses and degrees, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Grading policy, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - ROTC, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Social Philosophy, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Special PhD program, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Accreditation, 1975
    - Northwestern accrediting, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Administration, 1974-1976
    - Annual Report to the President, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Vice President - Business and Finance, 1976 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Admissions, 1974-1975
    - Enrollment, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Transfers, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Departments, and Schools, 1972
    - Title IX (regulation implementing), 1972 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Research, 1966-1979
    - Sponsored projects statistical trends report, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - Sponsored projects statistical trends report, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - Interim report on sponsored research projects and instruction, expenditures, 1966-1967 (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - Interim report on sponsored research projects and instruction, expenditures, 1967-1968 (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - Interim report on sponsored research projects and instruction, expenditures, 1968 (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - Interim report on sponsored research projects and instruction, expenditures, 1968-1969 (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - Interim report on sponsored research projects and instruction, expenditures, 1968 Nov-1969 (Box 11, Folder 21)
    - Interim report on sponsored research projects and instruction, expenditures, 1969 Feb-1970 (Box 11, Folder 22)
    - Interim report on sponsored research projects and instruction, expenditures, 1969 May-1970 (Box 11, Folder 23)
    - Interim report on sponsored research projects and instruction, expenditures, 1969 Nov-1970 (Box 11, Folder 24)
    - Interim report on sponsored research projects and instruction, expenditures, 1971 Feb-1972 (Box 11, Folder 25)
    - Interim report on sponsored research projects and instruction, expenditures, 1973 Feb-1974 (Box 11, Folder 26)
    - Sponsored project report, 1969 Aug 31 (Box 11, Folder 27)
    - Sponsored project report, 1970 Aug 31 (Box 11, Folder 28)
    - School of Humanities and Sciences, space needs, 1968-1978 (Box 11, Folder 29)
    - 01-600T Center for East Asian Studies, Undated (Box 11, Folder 30)
    - 07-302 Medical Center - centra1 courtyard, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 31)
    - 07 Medical School, addiction laboratory, 1971-1972 (Box 11, Folder 32)
    - 90-918 701 Welch Road, 1971-1976 (Box 11, Folder 33)
    - 90-931 851 Welch Road, 1970-1973 (Box 11, Folder 34)
    - 07-300 Medical Center, Animal Research Center, 1964-1970 (Box 11, Folder 35)
    - Budget meetings, 1973-1974 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Budget meetings, 1974-1975 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Budget meetings, 1975-1976 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Budget meetings, 1977-1978 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Budget process: miscellaneous background material, 1973-1974 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Stanford Board of Trustees - Committee on Finance and Development, reference manual, Undated (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - LRF documentation, 1970-1979 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - LRF workpapers, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - LRF economic context, 1977 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Stanford University Libraries budget letter, 1977-1978 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Budget staff and budget group meetings, 1976-1977 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Budget meetings, 1976-1977 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Budget process, 1976-1977 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Budget process, 1976-1977 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Review of Budget forms, 1977-1978 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Budget making, 1976-1977 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Budget making, 1976-1977 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - L. W. Price budget process, notes, 1978-1979 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Word graphics - plates for "Tabulation of Responses to Freshmen Parents' Questionnaire", 1978 (Box 15)
    - Budget process, 1975-1976 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Budget, budget meetings, 1975-1976 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Faculty salaries, 1975-1976 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Budget protocols, 1973-1974 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Student tuition, family income, faculty salaries, budgeting, 1974-1975 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Restricted funds, Undated (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - October revisions, 1974-1975 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Medical School Budget, 1978-1979 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Notes of Budget Equilibrium Program, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Notes on Operating Budget, 1977-1978 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Closed funds, Undated
    Individual folders are undated.
    - 1 RBA 611 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - 1 RBZ 657 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - 1 RBZ 658 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - 2 RBZ 604 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - 1 RBA 611 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - 1 RBZ 658 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - 1 RBZ 676 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Budget recommendations, 1967-1978
    - 3 QBA 001 Hoover, 1974-1978 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - 3 QAZ 001 Hoover, 1975-1978 (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - 1 MDA 001, 1967-1977 (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - 1 RBG 006, 1967-1977 (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - 1 RBZ 042, 1967-1977 (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - 2 RBZ 001, 1967-1977 (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - 7 RBE 032, 1976-1978 (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - 7 RBZ 017, 1976-1977 (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - 7 RBZ 067, 1976-1977 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Budget Worksheets, 1979-1980
    - Admissions (Box 17, Folder 17)
    - ARLO (Box 17, Folder 18)
    - CRIS (Box 17, Folder 19)
    - DAPER (Box 17, Folder 20)
    - Dean of Student Affairs (Box 17, Folder 21)
    - Development (Box 17, Folder 22)
    - Education (Box 17, Folder 23)
    - Earth Sciences (Box 17, Folder 24)
    - Engineering (Box 17, Folder 25)
    - Faculty Affirmative Action Fund (Box 17, Folder 26)
    - Financial Aid Administration (Box 17, Folder 27)
    - Financial Aid (Box 17, Folder 28)
    - Graduate School of Business (Box 17, Folder 29)
    - Hoover Institution (Box 17, Folder 30)
    - Humanities and Sciences (Box 17, Folder 31)
    - Independent Labs and Institutes (Box 17, Folder 32)
    - Law School (Box 17, Folder 33)
    - Libraries (Box 17, Folder 34)
    - Medicine (Box 17, Folder 35)
    - Memorial Church (Box 17, Folder 36)
    - Overseas Studies (Box 17, Folder 37)
    - President's/Provost's Office (Box 17, Folder 38)
    - Provost's Computing Fund (Box 17, Folder 39)
    - Public Affairs (Box 17, Folder 40)
    - Registrar (Box 17, Folder 41)
    - SCIP (Box 17, Folder 42)
    - SLAC (Box 17, Folder 43)
    - Summer Session (Box 17, Folder 44)
    - Undergraduate Studies (Box 17, Folder 45)
    - University Counsel (Box 17, Folder 46)
  - Investment Funds Report, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Endowment notes (RFB), 1975 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Privacy Panel, 1979 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Chicano Affairs (Assistant to the President), 1972-1973 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Chicano Affairs (Assistant to the President), 1973-1974 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Chicano Affairs, restructuring of Asst. to the the Pres. position, Undated (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Chicano Studies Research Institute, Undated (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Chicano seminar program, Undated (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Chicano affairs general, Undated (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Faculty data file, undated (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Faculty staff housing white paper, 1979 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Committee on Faculty and Staff Affairs, 1978-1979 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Joint Subcommitee on Faculty and Staff Housing, 1978-1979 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Schedule C- 9, plant services, University Press, reprographics, SCIT, Undated (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Model for Planning Transition to Equilibrium on University Budgets (BEP), 1975 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - APC - Stanford Overseas Studies Program, 1980 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Miscellaneous university budget proposals, Yale, Brown, Columbia w/Stanford Financial Aid, 1977-1978 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Budget Advisory Committee meetings, 1978-1979 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Long range financial forecast, 1975-1976 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Indirect cost recovery, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - Appointment, reappointment and promotion process - schedule of meetings, Undated (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - University Budget Priorities Advisory Commission, Undated
    Most folders are undated, exceptions are noted in the folder listing.
    - Membership meetings/agendas, etc (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Business and Finance: Facilities construction, personnel and employee relations (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Departmental reports to Deans (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Commission materials (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Budget equilibrium, 1976-1977 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Budget protocol, 1976-1977 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Gap closing central initiatives (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Publicity (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Faculty suggestions/others (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - Task Force I reports and correspondence (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - Task Force II reports and correspondence (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - Task Force III reports and correspondence (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - Task Force IV reports and correspondence (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - Task Force V reports and correspondence (Box 19, Folder 14)
    - Task Force VI reports and correspondence (Box 19, Folder 15)
    - Background materials for CROC Report, 1972 Dec (Box 19, Folder 16)
    - Committee on Faculty and Staff Affairs, general (Box 19, Folder 17)
    - Committee on Faculty and Staff Affairs, child care (Box 19, Folder 18)
    - Committee on Faculty and Staff Affairs, health (Box 19, Folder 19)
    - Committee on Faculty and Staff Affairs, health subcommittee (Box 19, Folder 20)
    - Committee on Faculty and Staff Affairs, housing (Box 19, Folder 21)
    - Committee on Faculty and Staff Affairs, life insurance (Box 19, Folder 22)
    - Committee on Faculty and Staff Affairs, LTD-SDI (Box 19, Folder 23)
    - Committee on Faculty and Staff Affairs, TIAA (Box 19, Folder 24)
    - Committee on Faculty and Staff Affairs, vacation (Box 19, Folder 25)
    - Minority admissions (RFB), 1975 (Box 19, Folder 26)
    - Operating budget guidelines book final work papers (RFB), 1976-1977 (Box 19, Folder 27)
    - Miscellaneous speeches - R.W. Lyman (RFB), 1979-1980 (Box 19, Folder 28)
  - Facilities files, 1960-1981
    - Quad 1, Building 1, General Administration, 1964-1967 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Quad 1, Building 1, Humanities and Sciences, 1963-1968 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Quad 1, Room 1, Graduate Division, 1960-1969 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - 1-1 Provost move, 1962-1971 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - 01- General main quad renovation, Undated (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - School of Humanities and Sciences - A Projection of Space Needs from 1965-1975 - Donald Price, Asst. Dean, 1965 Oct 1 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - School of Humanities and Sciences - A Projection of Space Needs from 1968-l978 - Donald Price, 1968 Jan 19 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - 01-1 Humanities and Sciences, Undated (Box 20, Folder 8)